#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/durga-sankar-dwibedy-732648141 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Scrum
Software Development
Requirements Analysis

Honors-Awards
CERTIFICATE OF ACHIEVEMENT
Star Performer

# Durga Sankar Dwibedy

DevOps Engineer / SRE at JK Tech Bengaluru

## Summary

An experienced Senior Product Development Engineer having 5+ years of experience with a demonstrated history of working in the Automotive, Semiconductor and E-Commerce Domain.

Skilled in DevOps, AWS, Python Scripting, Unix/Windows, MS-SQL, Agile(Scrum), ITIL. Strong engineering professional with a Post Graduate focused in MCA from Institute of Technical Education & Research.

## Experience

JK Tech
DevOps Engineer / SRE
March 2021 - Present (1 year)
Bangalore Urban, Karnataka, India

#### UST

Senior Product Development Engineer November 2019 - March 2021 (1 year 5 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Ascendum Solutions
Senior Software Engineer
September 2015 - November 2019 (4 years 3 months)
Bengaluru Area, India

Having extensive experience on Automotive domain. Worked with Volvo Group IT.

Worked as a SME for 6 web based applications.

Extensive hands on experience on L2 Level Application and Production support.

Worked as a Tech Lead and was leading a group of 7 associates.

Handled different DevOps operations along with AWS cloud as well as some on-premise Servers.

Was involved in setting up the complete Devops tools from the scratch and scheduling different jobs.

Worked as a Business Analyst for 11-12 months.

Having extensive experience on MS-SQL.

Extensive experience on complete ITIL process(i.e-User service Request, Incident Management, Problem Management, Change Management etc.) Experience into handling global clients and an interaction specialist at any level.

Extensive experience in driving MIM calls, CAB calls, Analyzing tickets trends and evaluation of KPIs.

### Education

Institute of Technial Education & Research Post Graduate, MCA · (2009 - 2012)

Utkal University
Bachelor's degree, BCA · (2006 - 2009)